Jacques Seligmann & Co.
Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
- Collectors Files, 1904-1977, undated, Series 2:; (Boxes 175-252; 35 linear feet)
  - Collectors, 1908, 1917-1977, 2.1:
    - Moyne, Lord (see Guinness, Walter Edward) (Box 196)
    - Mühlfeld, 1928, 1932 (Box 196, Folder 20)
    - Munn, Mrs. Ector, circa 1929, undated (Box 196, Folder 21)
    - Murat, Comtesse (née Bianchi), 1933, circa 1953, undated (Box 196, Folder 22)
    - Murat, S. A. Princesse (née Cécile Ney d'Elchingen), undated (Box 196, Folder 23)
    - Murphy, Dr. George E., 1954-1973, undated (Box 196, Folder 24)
    - Miscellaneous M, 1925-1971, undated (Box 196, Folder 25)
    - Namm, Benjamin H., 1924 (Box 196, Folder 26)
    - Nast, Condé, 1927-1942 (Box 196, Folder 27)
    - Nathan, Dr. Fritz, 1947 (Box 196, Folder 28)
    - Nathan, Dr. Peter, 1950-1968, undated, (2 folders) (Box 196, Folder 29-30)
    - Neal, W. Keith, undated (Box 197, Folder 1)
    - Neave, Sir A.T.C., circa 1957 (Box 197, Folder 2)
    - Nelson, Nicholas J., 1927 (Box 197, Folder 3)
    - Nesi, Pierre F., 1911, 1927-1963, undated (Box 197, Folder 4)
    - Netcher, Gladys, 1927, undated (Box 197, Folder 5)
    - Neumans, Gaston, 1919-1927 (Box 197, Folder 6)
    - New Gallery, 1957 (Box 197, Folder 7)
    - Newbauer, Peter, 1959 (Box 197, Folder 8)
    - Newberry, John S., Jr., 1941-1947, 1960, undated (Box 197, Folder 9)
    - Newhouse Galleries, 1937-1940, undated (Box 197, Folder 10)
    - Newton, Leon S., 1957-1960 (Box 197, Folder 11)
    - Newton, Maurice, undated (Box 197, Folder 12)
    - Nicholas, C. W., Jr., undated (Box 197, Folder 13)
    - Nitze, Paul H., undated (Box 197, Folder 14)
    - Miscellaneous N, 1938-1959, undated (Box 197, Folder 15)
    - Oakes, Harry, 1937 (Box 197, Folder 16)
    - O'Brien, John, 1967-1973, undated (Box 197, Folder 17)
    - Oettingen-Wallerstein, S. H. Prinz, 1928-1935 (Box 197, Folder 18)
    - Olavarrio & Co., 1955-1957 (Box 197, Folder 19)
    - Ollivier, M. B., undated (Box 197, Folder 20)
    - Oppenheimer, Dr. Adler, 1924, 1936, undated (Box 197, Folder 21)
    - Ordway, Miss Katherine, circa 1948 (Box 197, Folder 22)
    - Osborne, Sidney, 1928, undated (Box 197, Folder 23)
    - Osuna, Duc de, 1926-1930 (Box 197, Folder 24)
    - O'Toole, James Saint Laurence, undated (Box 197, Folder 25)
    - Oulmont, Charles, 1928, 1956, undated (Box 197, Folder 26)
    - Owen, Mrs. Kenneth Dale (Box 197)
      - Photographs, 1971-1974, undated (Box 197, Folder 27)
      - Research Material, 1966-1975, undated (Box 197, Folder 28)
    - Oxford University, 1931, circa 1960 (Box 198, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous O, 1925-circa 1961, undated (Box 198, Folder 2)
    - P. W. French & Co., Inc., 1919-1922, 1969-1976, undated (Box 198, Folder 3)
    - Pach, Walter, undated (Box 198, Folder 4)
    - Pagano, Piero (see also Rubinacci Antichita [gallery]), 1932, 1955-1974 (Box 198, Folder 5)
    - Paley, Mrs., 1963 (Box 198, Folder 6)
    - Paley, William S., 1935-1937 (Box 198, Folder 7)
    - Palmer, Mrs. Potter, undated (Box 198, Folder 8)
    - Paris Sales (Box 198)
      - Furniture, 1936, 1950, undated (Box 198, Folder 9)
      - Miscellaneous, 1900, 1936-1937, undated (Box 198, Folder 10)
      - Objects Sold Abroad, 1925-1928, 1936, undated (Box 198, Folder 11)
      - Painting and Drawings, 1927-1953 (Box 198, Folder 12)
      - Painting and Drawings, undated (Box 198, Folder 13)
      - Tapestries, 1928, undated (Box 198, Folder 14)
    - Paris Stock (Box 198)
      - Furniture, 1937, undated (Box 198, Folder 15)
      - Objets d'Art, 1935-1936, undated (Box 198, Folder 16)
      - Paintings and Drawings, 1935-1938 (Box 199, Folder 1)
      - Paintings and Drawings, undated (Box 199, Folder 2)
      - Sculpture, Ivories, 1936-1937, undated (Box 199, Folder 3)
      - Tapestries, 1946, undated (Box 199, Folder 4)
      - Items Destroyed in Fire, 1930-1931 (Box 199, Folder 5)
    - Parke, Harry G., 1971 (Box 199, Folder 6)
    - Parke-Bernet Galleries, Inc., 1944, 1957, undated (Box 199, Folder 7)
    - Parmalee, Mr. and Mrs. James, 1927, 1955 (Box 199, Folder 8)
    - Parry, Maj. Ernest Gambier, 1923-1967 (Box 199, Folder 9)
    - Parson, Miss M., 1929 (Box 199, Folder 10)
    - Passavant, Baron Herman (Box 199)
      - German Correspondence, 1929-1930 (Box 199, Folder 11)
      - Miscellaneous Correspondence and Notes, 1929-1930, undated (Box 199, Folder 12)
    - Pastré, Comte Andre and Comtesse Charles de Vogué (née Diane Pastré), 1929-1936, 1956, undated (Box 199, Folder 13)
    - Payson, Mrs. Charles Shipman, circa 1947, 1974, undated (Box 199, Folder 14)
    - Pecci-Blunt, Count Cecil, undated (Box 199, Folder 15)
    - Peel, David, 1967-1973 (Box 199, Folder 16)
    - Pellerin, August, 1936 (Box 199, Folder 17)
    - Pembroke, Earl of, 1928-1929, undated (Box 199, Folder 18)
    - Penrose, Spencer, 1929, 1942, undated (Box 199, Folder 19)
    - Perdoux, Yves, 1921-1924 (Box 199, Folder 20)
    - Pereire Family, 1931-1934, 1950, undated (Box 199, Folder 21)
    - Perls, Hugo, 1959, undated (Box 199, Folder 22)
    - Perry, Marsden J., undated (Box 199, Folder 23)
    - Personnaz, Antonin, 1930-1931 (Box 199, Folder 24)
    - Petin, Hector, 1925-1926, undated (Box 199, Folder 25)
    - Petscek, Otto, 1930-1931 (Box 199, Folder 26)
    - Peyta, Paul, 1929, undated (Box 199, Folder 27)
    - Peytel, Pierre, undated (Box 199, Folder 28)
    - Pforzheimer, Walter, 1928-1950, 1975, undated (Box 200, Folder 1)
    - Phillips, Mr. and Mrs. Elliot Schuyler, undated (Box 200, Folder 2)
    - Phipps, Howard, undated (Box 200, Folder 3)
    - Phipps, Mr. and Mrs. John S., undated (Box 200, Folder 4)
    - Phipps, Mrs. Ogden, 1939 (Box 200, Folder 5)
    - Pick, Grant J., 1958-1961 (Box 200, Folder 6)
    - Pijoan, Joseph, 1954 (Box 200, Folder 7)
    - Pitcairn, Raymond, 1920-1932 (Box 200, Folder 8)
    - Pitcairn, Theodore, 1938-1944 (Box 200, Folder 9)
    - Plandiura, Luis, 1923-1925 (Box 200, Folder 10)
    - Plantevignes, Camille, 1930 (Box 200, Folder 11)
    - Poix, Princesse de, 1930-circa 1932 (Box 200, Folder 12)
    - Polignac, Duc de, circa 1926-1933, 1963 (Box 200, Folder 13)
    - Polovtsoff, [Alexandre], 1934 (Box 200, Folder 14)
    - Pontremoli, Mme. Emmanuel, 1937 (Box 200, Folder 15)
    - Porges, Otto, 1959 (Box 200, Folder 16)
    - Porter, Mrs. George F., 1972 (Box 200, Folder 17)
    - Post, Mrs. J., undated (Box 200, Folder 18)
    - Post, Marjorie Merriweather (Mrs. E. F. Hutton), circa 1955, undated (Box 200, Folder 19)
    - Potocki, Comte Alfred, 1928 (Box 200, Folder 20)
    - Powis, Earl of, circa 1953, 1957, undated (Box 200, Folder 21)
    - Powney, Christopher, 1924, 1961-1969, undated (Box 200, Folder 22)
    - Pratt, Mrs. Harold Irving, 1936, 1942, undated (Box 200, Folder 23)
    - Prentice, Mrs. John P., undated (Box 200, Folder 24)
    - Preuschen, Baron Gerhard Freiherr von (see von Preuschen, Baron Gerhard Freiherr) (Box 200)
    - Prince of Liechtenstein (see Leichtenstein Collection) (Box 200)
    - Proehl, Ernst, 1927-circa 1930 (Box 200, Folder 25)
    - Pulitzer, Joseph, Jr., 1954-1957, undated (Box 200, Folder 26)
    - Putzel, Howard, undated (Box 200, Folder 27)
    - Pyrie, Percy R., undated (Box 200, Folder 28)
    - Miscellaneous P, 1929-1973, undated (Box 200, Folder 29)
    - Quenneville, Chantal, 1931-1934, undated (Box 200, Folder 30)
    - Quinn, Mrs. Charles H., 1928-1929, undated (Box 200, Folder 31)
    - Miscellaneous Q, circa 1955-1958, undated (Box 200, Folder 32)
    - Radnor, Earl of, 1931-circa 1955, undated (Box 200, Folder 33)
    - Rains Gallery, undated (Box 200, Folder 34)
    - Ramage, Alfred H., 1924-1973, undated (Box 200, Folder 35)
    - Rasini, Giovanni, circa 1949, undated (Box 200, Folder 36)
    - Rasmussen, George (Box 201)
      - Paintings and Drawings, 1926-1930, undated (Box 201, Folder 1)
      - Furniture and Objets d'Art, 1924-circa 1938, undated (Box 201, Folder 2)
    - Ratoff, Mrs. Gregory, undated (Box 201, Folder 3)
    - Ratton, Charles, 1958, 1963 (Box 201, Folder 4)
    - Rebay, Baroness Hilla von (see von Rebay, Baroness Hilla) (Box 201)
    - Reed, Orel P., 1957-1960 (Box 201, Folder 5)
    - Reichold, Henry, 1932-1938, undated (Box 201, Folder 6)
    - Reid, Mrs. Whitelaw, undated (Box 201, Folder 7)
    - Renand, Georges, 1951, undated (Box 201, Folder 8)
    - Renders Collection, 1936, circa 1956 (Box 201, Folder 9)
    - Resor, Mr. and Mrs. Stanley, 1927, undated (Box 201, Folder 10)
    - Reves, Emery, 1955, undated (Box 201, Folder 11)
    - Rewald, John, 1959 (Box 201, Folder 12)
    - Richard, Harold C., 1928-1930 (Box 201, Folder 13)
    - Riddle, Mrs. John Wallace, 1939 (Box 201, Folder 14)
    - Rieth, Dr. Kurt, 1954-circa 1956 (Box 201, Folder 15)
    - Robbins, Mrs. (formerly Mrs. André Seligmann), 1951-1956, undated (Box 201, Folder 16)
    - Robertson, Gen. and Mrs. Ralph K., 1958, undated (Box 201, Folder 17)
    - Robinson, Edward G., 1938, 1957, undated (Box 201, Folder 18)
    - Rockefeller, Mrs. John D., Jr., 1936, 1958, undated (Box 201, Folder 19)
    - Rockefeller, Mrs. Nelson A., 1964-1965 (Box 201, Folder 20)
    - Rockmore, Miss, 1930 (Box 201, Folder 21)
    - Roesler, Norbert L. H., 1969 (Box 201, Folder 22)
    - Roger-Marx, Claude, 1929, 1938, 1956, undated (Box 201, Folder 23)
    - Rogers, Mary Benjamin, 1951, 1956, undated (Box 201, Folder 24)
    - Rogerson, James C., undated (Box 201, Folder 25)
    - Rose, Billy, 1947-1955, undated (Box 201, Folder 26)
    - Roseberry, Earl of, 1925-1926, undated (Box 201, Folder 27)
    - Rosenbaum, Mrs. Joseph H., 1940, 1945, undated (Box 201, Folder 28)
    - Rosenberg, Pierre, 1961-1963, undated (Box 201, Folder 29)
    - Rosenberg & Stiebel (Box 201)
      - Miscellaneous Objets d'Art, 1948, 1957, undated (Box 201, Folder 30)
      - Samson and the Lion Bronze, 1930-1959, undated (Box 201, Folder 31)
    - Rosenfeld, Ernst, 1927-1933, 1959, undated (Box 202, Folder 1)
    - Rosenthal, Moritz, undated (Box 202, Folder 2)
    - Rosenwald, Lessing J., 1940-1941, undated (Box 202, Folder 3)
    - Rosenwald, Richard M., undated (Box 202, Folder 4)
    - Rothbart, Albert, 1929, undated (Box 202, Folder 5)
    - Rothschild, Baron Edouard de, 1919, 1929-circa 1967, undated (Box 202, Folder 6)
    - Rothschild, Mrs. Robert F., 1973 (Box 202, Folder 7)
    - Rouart, Ernest Louis and Denis, circa 1949, 1951, undated (Box 202, Folder 8)
    - Roullier Gallery (see Albert Roullier Art Galleries) (Box 202)
    - Rubinacci Antichita (gallery; see also Pagano, Piero), 1974 (Box 202, Folder 9)
    - Ruspoli, Prince Edmondo and Princess Virginia, 1956, undated (Box 202, Folder 10)
    - Russell, Mrs. Charles H., Jr., 1929, 1943, undated (Box 202, Folder 11)
    - Russell, Faris, undated (Box 202, Folder 12)
    - Rust, 1960 (Box 202, Folder 13)
    - Ruxton, Mr. and Mrs. Philip, undated (Box 202, Folder 14)
    - Ryan, Thomas F., 1909-1926, undated (Box 203, Folder 1)
    - Ryerson, Mrs. Joseph T., 1949, undated (Box 203, Folder 2)
    - Ryle, Dorothy, 1928-1937 (Box 203, Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous R, 1916-circa 1965, undated (Box 203, Folder 4)
    - Sabin, Frank T. (see also De Koenigsberg, Mrs. P.), 1928-1929, undated (Box 203, Folder 5)
    - Sachs, Arthur (Box 203)
      - Goya, The Bullfight, 1951-1956, undated (Box 203, Folder 6)
      - Titian, Adoration of the Magi and Portrait of a Man, 1940-1949, undated, (2 folders) (Box 203, Folder 7-8)
      - Miscellaneous Collection Pieces, 1922-1965, undated (Box 203, Folder 9)
    - Sachs, Edith, 1929, undated (Box 203, Folder 10)
    - Sachs, Harry, 1923-1936, undated (Box 203, Folder 11)
    - Sachs, Howard, undated (Box 203, Folder 12)
    - Sachs, Paul, circa 1965, undated (Box 203, Folder 13)
    - Safron, Max, 1936 (Box 203, Folder 14)
    - Saidenberg Gallery, undated (Box 203, Folder 15)
    - Salomon, William, 1912-1923, undated (Box 203, Folder 16)
    - Samuel H. Kress Foundation (Box 204)
      - Acquisitions: General Notes and Lists, 1950, undated (Box 204, Folder 1)
      - Acquisitions: Mantegna, 1930-1950, undated (Box 204, Folder 2)
      - Acquisitions: Bellini, Giovanni, 1929-1932 (Box 204, Folder 3)
      - Acquisitions: Bellini, Giovanni, 1948-1950 (Box 204, Folder 4)
      - Acquisitions: Bellini, Giovanni, undated (Box 204, Folder 5)
      - Acquisitions: Vigée LeBrun, 1934-1950, undated (Box 204, Folder 6)
      - Acquisitions: Retascon Master, 1937-1950, undated (Box 204, Folder 7)
      - Acquisitions: Bouchardon, 1948-1950, undated (Box 204, Folder 8)
      - Acquisitions: Coysevox, 1948-1951, undated (Box 204, Folder 9)
      - Acquisitions: Houdon, 1934, 1950-1952, undated (Box 204, Folder 10)
      - Acquisitions: Fragonard, 1951-1963, undated (Box 205, Folder 1)
      - Acquisitions: Giovanni da Bologna, 1950-1952, undated (Box 205, Folder 2)
      - Acquisitions: Ile de France, Trinity, 1951-1954, 1969-1971, undated (Box 205, Folder 3)
      - Acquisitions: French 15th Century, St. Christopher, 1951-1953, undated (Box 205, Folder 4)
      - Acquisitions: DesJardins, circa 1968, undated (Box 205, Folder 5)
      - Acquisitions: Cagnacci (Canlassi), 1954, undated (Box 205, Folder 6)
      - Acquisitions: Ile de France, Madonna and Child, 1956, 1966, undated (Box 205, Folder 7)
      - Acquisitions: Schaffner, 1932, 1955-1957, undated (Box 205, Folder 8)
      - Acquisitions: Sculpture, Collection of the Prince of Liechtenstein, 1953-1954, 1971, undated (Box 205, Folder 9)
      - Acquisitions: Acting as Agent for A. Sachs, 1943, undated (Box 205, Folder 10)
      - Acquisitions: Acting as Agent for the Mackay Estate, 1924-1944, undated (Box 205, Folder 11)
      - Correspondence, 1930-1956 (Box 205, Folder 12)
      - Personal Collection, 1924, undated (Box 205, Folder 13)
      - Printed Matter, 1926, 1957-1967, undated (Box 205, Folder 14)
    - Sandblom, Philip, circa 1958 (Box 206, Folder 1)
    - Sandwich, Earl of, circa 1929-1934 (Box 206, Folder 2)
    - Santamarina, Sen. Antonio, 1942, undated (Box 206, Folder 3)
    - Sardi, Eugenio, 1928 (Box 206, Folder 4)
    - Sassoon, Ms. Meyer, circa 1955 (Box 206, Folder 5)
    - Sassoon, Philip (Trent House), circa 1931-1934 (Box 206, Folder 6)
    - Satinover, Joseph, 1923 (Box 206, Folder 7)
    - Satterwhite, Dr. Preston Pope, 1929-1930, undated (Box 206, Folder 8)
    - Schaumburg-Lippe, Prince Adolph, 1929 (Box 206, Folder 9)
    - Schempp, Theodore, 1940-1947, undated (Box 206, Folder 10)
    - Schiff, John M. (Box 206)
      - Drawings and Paintings, 1938-1939, 1942, undated, (2 folders) (Box 206, Folder 11-12)
      - Persian Potteries, 1950-1957, undated (Box 206, Folder 13)
      - Miscellaneous Collection Items, 1920-1942, undated (Box 206, Folder 14)
    - Schiff, Mortimer L., 1906-1907 (Box 206, Folder 15)
    - Schiff, Mortimer L., 1923-1929, 1938, undated (Box 206, Folder 16)
    - Schimmel, Norbert, 1957-1958 (Box 207, Folder 1)
    - Schinasi, Leon, 1925 (Box 207, Folder 2)
    - Schloss Oels (Collection of Crown Prince), 1929-1930 (Box 207, Folder 3)
    - Schloss Sigmaringen, 1928-1931, undated (Box 207, Folder 4)
    - Schmid, Alwin, circa 1926 (Box 207, Folder 5)
    - Schmidlapp, Mrs. Carl J., undated (Box 207, Folder 6)
    - Schmitz, Edouard, 1930-1935, undated (Box 207, Folder 7)
    - Schmitz-Hille, Peter, 1955-1973, undated (Box 207, Folder 8)
    - Schniewind, Henry, Jr., undated (Box 207, Folder 9)
    - Schöttle, Rüdigger, 1970-1973 (Box 207, Folder 10)
    - Schuette, Mrs. Robert W., 1926 (Box 207, Folder 11)
    - Schulenburg Collection, 1962-1970 (Box 207, Folder 12)
    - Schulthess, Hans von (see von Schulthess, Hans) (Box 207)
    - Schwarbacher, Alfred, 1941, 1955 (Box 207, Folder 13)
    - Sciolette, H. L., 1949, 1955, undated (Box 207, Folder 14)
    - Scott, Maj. Alfred I., undated (Box 207, Folder 15)
    - Scott, Rufus W., undated (Box 207, Folder 16)
    - Seligman, James, 1925-1935, 1959, undated (Box 207, Folder 17)
    - Seligmann, Armand, 1945 (Box 207, Folder 18)
    - Seligmann, François-Gerard, 1947-1967, undated (Box 207, Folder 19)
    - Seligmann, Jaqueline, 1935-1948, undated (Box 207, Folder 20)
    - Seligmann, René, 1936, undated (Box 207, Folder 21)
    - Semcesen, W., 1958 (Box 207, Folder 22)
    - Severin, Erik, 1927, 1931 (Box 207, Folder 23)
    - Shallcross, Mr. and Mrs. Cecil F., undated (Box 207, Folder 24)
    - Sharpe, Mrs. Henry D., undated (Box 207, Folder 25)
    - Sherman, Irving H., 1936, circa 1942, undated (Box 207, Folder 26)
    - Sibilat, R., 1918, 1933, undated (Box 207, Folder 27)
    - Sickles, Daniel, 1928, 1938, undated (Box 207, Folder 28)
    - Sieff, Israel M., undated (Box 207, Folder 29)
    - Silberberg, Daniel H., 1916 (Box 207, Folder 30)
    - Silo's (auction house), undated (Box 207, Folder 31)
    - Simmons, Percy, 1967-1970 (Box 208, Folder 1)
    - Simon, Eduard, 1928-1929, undated (Box 208, Folder 2)
    - Simon, Norman and Jennifer, 1974-1975, undated (Box 208, Folder 3)
    - Simonds, W. R., circa 1929 (Box 208, Folder 4)
    - Simpson, John W., 1917-1936, circa 1955, undated (Box 208, Folder 5)
    - Singer, Mrs. Cecil M., 1956-1965, undated (Box 208, Folder 6)
    - Sloane, H. T., undated (Box 208, Folder 7)
    - Smith, Mrs. John T., undated (Box 208, Folder 8)
    - Smith, Mrs. Oswald, 1933 (Box 208, Folder 9)
    - Snellenberg, Joseph N., undated (Box 208, Folder 10)
    - Snyder, Henry S., undated (Box 208, Folder 11)
    - Soifer, Nathaniel, 1959-1961, undated (Box 208, Folder 12)
    - Sola Cabiati, Comte, 1929-1930 (Box 208, Folder 13)
    - Soler, Ignacio, 1928-1933, 1956 (Box 208, Folder 14)
    - Solomon, Mr. and Mrs. Arthur K., 1955, undated (Box 208, Folder 15)
    - Solomon, Barbara, 1974 (Box 208, Folder 16)
    - Sonnenberg, Benjamin, 1960-1974, undated (Box 208, Folder 17)
    - Sormani, Comte Alessandro, 1930 (Box 208, Folder 18)
    - Spaulding, John T., 1930, undated (Box 208, Folder 19)
    - Speelman, Edward, circa 1951-1957, undated (Box 208, Folder 20)
    - Spencer, Earl of, circa 1963, undated (Box 208, Folder 21)
    - Spencer-Churchill, Capt. Edward S., circa 1935-1964, undated (Box 208, Folder 22)
    - Spiro, Stephen B., 1962-1971, undated (Box 208, Folder 23)
    - Spreckels, Mrs. Adolph, undated (Box 208, Folder 24)
    - Sprink, Walter, 1965-1970 (Box 208, Folder 25)
    - Spuehler, Marie, 1959 (Box 208, Folder 26)
    - Stang, J. B., 1928-1929, undated (Box 208, Folder 27)
    - Staub-Terlinden, Mrs. E., 1932, undated (Box 208, Folder 28)
    - Steegmuller, Francis, undated (Box 208, Folder 29)
    - Stehli, Emil, 1938, 1942, 1953 (Box 208, Folder 30)
    - Stein, Mr. and Mrs. Edgar, 1936, undated (Box 208, Folder 31)
    - Stein, Gertrude, 1938-1939 (Box 208, Folder 32)
    - Steinberg, Mrs. Mark, undated (Box 208, Folder 33)
    - Steiner, John H., 1966-1972 (Box 208, Folder 34)
    - Stern, Mrs. and Mrs. Benjamin, 1922-1931, undated (Box 209, Folder 1)
    - Stern, Jean, 1938 (Box 209, Folder 2)
    - Sternberg, Josef von (see von Sternberg, Josef) (Box 209)
    - Stettenheim, I. M., 1928, undated (Box 209, Folder 3)
    - Stift Neubourg, 1926 (Box 209, Folder 4)
    - Stift Nonnberg, 1924-1930 (Box 209, Folder 5)
    - Stirling, Col. William, 1950-circa 1958, undated (Box 209, Folder 6)
    - Stoclet, Adolphe, 1924, 1931, 1963, undated (Box 209, Folder 7)
    - Stoll, Mrs. Barry V., 1972 (Box 209, Folder 8)
    - Stora, Raphael, 1929 (Box 209, Folder 9)
    - Storrs, Mr. and Mrs. Frank V., 1952, undated (Box 209, Folder 10)
    - Stotesbury, Edward T., undated (Box 209, Folder 11)
    - Straight, Michael, 1957-1972, undated (Box 209, Folder 12)
    - Stralem, Donald S., undated (Box 209, Folder 13)
    - Stransky, Josef, undated (Box 209, Folder 14)
    - Straus, Herbert N. and Therese K. (Box 209)
      - Drawings and Paintings, 1926-1974, undated, (4 folders) (Box 209, Folder 15-18)
      - Enamels, 1926 (Box 210, Folder 1)
      - Furniture, undated (Box 210, Folder 2)
      - Photograph of Herbert N. Straus, undated (Box 210, Folder 3)
      - Sculpture, Italian 15th Century, Small Bronze Group, 1926-1927, undated (Box 210, Folder 4)
      - Sculpture, Verrocchio, 1927-1950 (Box 210, Folder 5)
      - Stone Vase, 1942, undated (Box 210, Folder 6)
      - Tapestries, 1931-1957, undated (Box 210, Folder 7)
    - Straus, Jesse I., 1910-1948, undated (Box 210, Folder 8)
    - Straus, Lionel F., 1943 (Box 210, Folder 9)
    - Straus, Nathan, undated (Box 210, Folder 10)
    - Straus, Mr. and Mrs. Percy S., 1926-1929, undated (Box 210, Folder 11)
    - Straus, Mrs. S. W., 1923 (Box 210, Folder 12)
    - Strauss, Jules, 1932 (Box 210, Folder 13)
    - Strolin, M. A., 1934, circa 1955 (Box 210, Folder 14)
    - Sturgess, Miss Dorothy, undated (Box 210, Folder 15)
    - Suarez, Mrs. Diego, 1938, undated (Box 210, Folder 16)
    - Sullivan, Mrs. Cornelius J., circa 1934, undated (Box 210, Folder 17)
    - Sulzbach, M., 1919, undated (Box 210, Folder 18)
    - Sweeney, James Johnson, 1943, circa 1953 (Box 210, Folder 19)
    - Swetzoff Gallery, 1957, undated (Box 210, Folder 20)
    - Miscellaneous S, circa 1926-1967, undated (Box 210, Folder 21)
    - Talbott, Mrs. Harold, undated (Box 211, Folder 1)
    - Tannahill, Robert H., 1927-1968 (Box 211, Folder 2)
    - Tate & Hall, 1929-1933, undated (Box 211, Folder 3)
    - Tauber Collection, 1934 (Box 211, Folder 4)
    - Taylor, Bertrand L., Jr., undated (Box 211, Folder 5)
    - Taylor, Mrs. D. Armstrong, 1926-1936 (Box 211, Folder 6)
    - Taylor, Jacqueline P., 1925 (Box 211, Folder 7)
    - Taylor, Dr. and Mrs. Kenneth, undated (Box 211, Folder 8)
    - Taylor, Myron C., 1923-1926 (Box 211, Folder 9)
    - Thacher, John S., circa 1957 (Box 211, Folder 10)
    - Théodore Collection, 1939, undated (Box 211, Folder 11)
    - Thompson, G. David, 1955 (Box 211, Folder 12)
    - Thompson, Mrs. W. Roosevelt, 1927-1929, 1959-1961, undated (Box 211, Folder 13)
    - Thorne, Mrs. Landon K. (Box 211)
      - Furniture, 1948 (Box 211, Folder 14)
      - Paintings, Drawings, and Sculpture, 1875, 1892, 1926-1934 (Box 211, Folder 15)
      - Daubigny, The Barge, 1961 (Box 211, Folder 16)
      - Delacroix, Jocob Wrestling with the Angel, 1956-1962 (Box 211, Folder 17)
      - Leoni, Portrait of a Cardinal, 1962 (Box 211, Folder 18)
      - Millet, Paysanne se Resposant dans la Forêt, 1962-1974 (Box 211, Folder 19)
      - Tortebat, Venus et les Graces, 1960 (Box 211, Folder 20)
      - Veinet, Arab on Horseback, 1955-1960 (Box 211, Folder 21)
      - Vouet, Portrait of a Young Man, 1960-1972 (Box 211, Folder 22)
    - Thorne, Mr. and Mrs. Oakleigh, undated (Box 211, Folder 23)
    - Thurkow Collection, circa 1955, undated (Box 211, Folder 24)
    - Thurn & Taxis-Metternich, Princess, 1927-1937 (Box 211, Folder 25)
    - Thyssen, Fritz, 1928, 1959, undated (Box 211, Folder 26)
    - Thyssen, Baron Heinrich, 1930-1972 (Box 211, Folder 27)
    - Timken, William R., 1927-1929, undated (Box 211, Folder 28)
    - Todhunter, Inc., undated (Box 211, Folder 29)
    - Tozzi, Piero, undated (Box 211, Folder 30)
    - Traumann, Enrique, 1958-1959 (Box 211, Folder 31)
    - Travers, Walter, undated (Box 211, Folder 32)
    - Trevor, Clyfford, 1905, 1912-circa 1947 (Box 211, Folder 33)
    - Trivulzio, Don Luigi Alberico, 1928-1935 (Box 211, Folder 34)
    - Tucker, Carll, 1924, 1974 (Box 211, Folder 35)
    - Tuffier, Dr., 1929, undated (Box 211, Folder 36)
    - Tweeddale, Marquess of, 1932 (Box 211, Folder 37)
    - Tyson, Carroll S., Jr., 1930 (Box 211, Folder 38)
    - Ullman, Charles, undated (Box 211, Folder 39)
    - Ulmer, Ernest, 1975 (Box 211, Folder 40)
    - Untermeyer, Milton F., undated (Box 211, Folder 41)
    - Unzue, Mme., 1916-1927, undated (Box 211, Folder 42)
    - Miscellaneous U, 1933, circa 1959, undated (Box 211, Folder 43)
    - Valentin, Curt, 1938 (Box 211, Folder 44)